myshadow.org 2016-04-04

# Privacy Policy | Me and my Shadow

# Privacy Policy

Myshadow.org Privacy Policy explains how Myshadow.org gathers and uses Users data when they visit Myshadow.org. 

### Website Visitors

Like most website operators, Myshadow.org collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Myshadow.org’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Myshadow.org’s visitors use its website. From time to time, Myshadow.org may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

Myshadow.org also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. Myshadow.org does not use such information to identify its visitors, however, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information, as described below.

### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to Myshadow.org’s websites choose to interact withMyshadow.org in ways that require Myshadow.org to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Myshadow.org gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who use our mailing lists to provide an email address. In each case, Myshadow.org collects such information only as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Myshadow.org. Myshadow.org does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

#### Myshadow.org will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone.

If you are a registered user of a Myshadow.org newsletter and have supplied your email address, Myshadow.org may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Myshadow.org. We primarily use our blog to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum.

Myshadow.org takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration, or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

### Aggregated Statistics

Myshadow.org may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, Myshadow.org may reveal how many downloads a particular file got, or say which versions are most popular based on checks from api.Myshadow.org, a web service used by Tacticaltech installations to check for new versions of Tacticaltech.

### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Myshadow.org uses cookies to help Myshadow.org identify and track visitors, their usage of Myshadow.org website, and their website access preferences. Myshadow.org visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Myshadow.org’s websites.

### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Myshadow.org may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Myshadow.org’s sole discretion. Myshadow.org encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

### Reusing this Privacy Policy

You are welcome to reuse and be inspired by this Privacy Policy after making sure it complies with the way your website tracks, uses and discloses users information.
